Friends, family, we're gathered to celebrate here today...
...the joyous union of Ross and Emily.
Now Ross, repeat after me.
I, Ross.
Take thee, Emily.
Take thee, Rachel.
Emily.
Heh. Emily.
Uh, shall I go on?
He said "Rachel," right?
Do you think I should go up there?
Yes. Yes. Do go on.
I think we'd better start again.
Ross, repeat after me.
I, Ross.
Take thee, Emily.
Ha, ha. Like there'd be anybody else.
As my lawfully wedded wife, in sickness and in health...
...till death parts us.
...until death parts us.
Really, I do. Emily.
Do you have the rings?
Emily, place this ring on Ross' finger...
...as a symbol of your bond everlasting.
Ross, place this ring...
...on Emily's hand as a symbol...
...of the love that encircles you forever.
Happy to.
They have made their declarations...
...and it gives me great pleasure to declare them husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
This is worse than when he married the lesbian.
Just keep smiling.
Okay...
Well, that went well. Yeah.
It could've been worse. He could've shot her.
Ha, ha. That was pretty funny, wasn't it?
You spoiled everything. It's like a nightmare.
All my friends and family are out there. How can I face them?
How could you do this to me?
Hey, no matter what happens with Ross and Emily...
...we still get cake, right?
That's all right. No, no. You take your time, sweetie.
I'll be out here. Ha, ha.
She's just fixing her makeup.
I hate you.
And I love you.
Boy, a bad time to say the wrong name, huh, Ross?
That's true. Thanks, Dad.
People should be dancing, huh?
Hey, this is a party. Come on.
Joey. Dance.
Yes, Waltham Interiors.
Hello, this is Ross Geller's personal physician, Dr. Phalange.
Who?
Yeah, I discovered that Ross forgot to take his brain medicine.
Um, now, without it, uh, in the brain of Ross...
...uh, women's names are interchangeable.
Through no fault of his own.
Oh, my God. Phoebe.
No, not Phoebe. Dr. Phalange.
Oh, no. You have it too.
Hello?
Hey.
Wow, I hope you don't take this the wrong way...
...but I know we had plans to meet up tonight and...
Ugh. I'm just kind of worried about what it might do to our friendship.
I know.
Ugh. How could we have let this happen?
Seven times.
You know, look. We were away.
In a foreign, romantic country.
Right.
I blame London.
Bad London.
So look, um...
...while we're still in London, I mean, we can keep doing it, right?
Well, I don't see that we have a choice.
But when we're back home, we don't do it.
Only here.
You know, I saw a wine cellar downstairs.
I'll meet you there in two minutes.
Okay.
Mon? Mon, I got to ask you something.
Now?
Ross said my name up there. I mean, come on.
I can't just pretend that didn't happen.
I don't know.
Monica, what should I do?
Just do the right thing.
What?
Tow the line. Thread the needle. Think outside the box.
Monica, wait, listen. I'm gonna talk to Ross about what he thinks it meant.
Wait. Rachel, no.
He's married.
Married.
If you don't realize that, I can't help you.
Okay. You're right.
You're right. You can't help me.
Jack, is it all our fault? Were we bad parents?
Yes.
Oh yeah? Well, who serves steak when there's no place to sit?
I mean, how are you supposed to eat this?
Hey, what's up?
Where were you? We were supposed to meet.
Forget it. That's off.
Why?
The next tour of the wine cellar...
...will commence in two minutes.
Joey, what are you doing?
You promised Phoebe no meat till she has the babies.
Well, I figured we're in another country, so it doesn't count.
That's true.
The man's got a point.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
I'm sorry things aren't working out so well.
Oh, no. Ha, ha. It could be better. It's gonna be okay, right?
Oh, yeah. Of course. I mean, she's gonna get over this, you know?
I mean, so you said my name.
You know, you just said it because you saw me there.
If you'd seen a circus freak, you would've said:
I take thee Circus Freak.
It didn't mean anything. It's just a mistake.
It didn't mean anything.
Right?
No, no.
Of course it didn't mean anything.
I mean, I can understand why Emily would think it meant something...
...you know, because it was you.
But it absolutely didn't. It didn't! It didn't!
Ross, hey, the band's ready outside for your first dance with Emily.
Oh. Oh, the band's ready.
Well, we got to do what the band says.
I don't care about the stupid band!
You spit on me, man.
I'm sorry.
Emily is taking kind of a long time, huh?
Heh.
When I locked myself in the bathroom at my wedding...
...it was because I was trying to pop the window out of the frame.
Right.
Get the hell out of there. You know?
Emily.
I'm coming in.
Oh, look at that. Same thing.
In the middle of everything...
...if I scream the word "yippee," just ignore me.
Huh! Oh, my God. Rachel.
Oh, hello, Rachel.
Ross said my name.
Okay? My name.
Ross said my name up there.
That obviously means that he still loves me.
Okay, don't believe me. I know I'm right.
All right. Do you guys want to go and get a drink?
Yes, we do.
But we have to change first.
Yes, I want to change.
Why don't you go get a table?
We'll be down in five minutes.
Fifteen minutes.
Ha, ha.
Hello.
Oh, Pheebs. It's Phoebe.
Oh, hey, hey.
Oh, great.
Hi.
So, what happened?
Well, Ross said my name.
Yeah, I know, but I don't think that means anything.
Okay, Pheebs, let's look at this objectively.
All right, ninth grade, right?
The obsession starts.
All right? Summer after ninth grade...
...he sees me in a two-piece for the first time.
His obsession begins to grow, right?
Hey, listen, why don't we go change in my room?
My clothes are... Oh.
Wow, you look...
No time for that.
Okay.
Hey, dude. Let me in. I got a girl out here.
Well, I've got a girl in here.
No, you don't. I just saw you go in there with Monica.
Well, we're hanging out in here.
Which one of us is gonna be having sex in there? Me or you?
Well, I suppose I would have to say you.
What if we're watching a movie in here?
Which we are.
And we've already paid for it. It's My Giant.
My Giant? I love that movie.
You really think this is okay?
Well, Ross and Emily aren't gonna use it.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Oh.
You know, I don't feel right about this.
Oh, Monica...
This is the honeymoon suite.
The room expects sex.
The room would be disappointed if it didn't get sex.
All the other honeymoon suites would think it was a loser.
Okay.
Emily?
Nope. Not under here.
You didn't find her?
No, I've looked everywhere.
Well, you couldn't have, or else you would've found her.
I think you should keep looking.
Yeah. For about, uh, 30 minutes?
Or 45?
Wow, in 45 minutes, you could find her twice.
No. For all I know, she's trying to find me...
...but couldn't because I kept moving around.
No, from now on, I'm staying in one place.
Right here.
It's getting late.
Yeah, We're going to go.
Actually...
...do you guys mind staying here for a while?
Ugh. You know, we got to get up early and catch that plane to New York.
Yeah, it's a very large plane.
That's cool.
But we'll stay here with you.
Thanks, guys. Ha, ha.
I really appreciate this, you know, but you don't need to rub my butt.
We have to leave for New York in an hour.
I know. I've been looking at those doors.
They look pretty soundproof, don't you think?
We can't do that. That's insane.
I mean, A, he could wake up. And B, you know...
...let's go for it.
Emily? Emily.
Emily!
Nope.
Forget about Emily. She's not with us.
We've come for her things.
Where is she?
She's in hiding. She's utterly humiliated. She doesn't want to see you ever again.
We're very sad that it didn't work out between you and Emily, monkey.
But I think you're absolutely delicious.
Excuse me, I'm standing right here.
Oh, yes.
There you are.
Hey. Hey, you guys. Hurry up. Get some. There's a whole cart outside.
Goodbye, Geller.
Now, hold on. Hold on.
Look, look. Your daughter and I...
...are supposed to leave tonight for our honeymoon.
Now, you tell her that I'm gonna be at that airport...
...and I hope that she'll be there too.
Yeah, I said Rachel's name, but it didn't mean anything.
She's just a friend. That's all. Now, look, just tell Emily I love her...
...and that I can't imagine spending my life with anyone else.
Please, promise me that you'll tell her that.
All right, I'll tell her.
Come on, bugger face.
Call me.
You spend half your life in the bathroom.
Why do you never go out the bloody window?
Well, maybe it's best we never got to do it again.
Yeah, it kind of makes that one night special.
You know, technically, we still are over international waters.
I'm going to the bathroom. Maybe I'll see you there in a bit?
Okay.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Uh, no.
Felicity and I, we were watching My Giant. And I was thinking...
...I'm never gonna be as good an actor as that giant.
Do you think I'm just wasting my life with this acting thing?
No.
I mean, the giant's like five years younger than me.
You know, you think I'll ever get there?
Yes.
Thanks, man.
Okay, man.
But what about how much taller he is than me?
I mean, there's no way I can make myself taller now.
And who knows what science will come up with in the future...
...but, Chandler, what if I die an unsuccessful, regular-size man?
Hey, Monica. Wow, you've been in the bathroom for, like, a half-hour.
I know.
Had the beef tips, huh?
Hey.
You ate meat!
You had sex!
No, we didn't.
I know you didn't.
I was talking about Monica.
Phoebe, I did not have sex.
Oh, this pregnancy is throwing me all off.
I'm gonna say hi to the chick and duck.
Oh, me too.
Why would you need to say hi? You've been feeding them for four days.
Oh, right. Maybe I'll just go home.
Well, we certainly are alone.
Good thing we have that "not New York" rule.
Right.
Um, listen, since we're on that subject...
...um, I just wanted to tell you that, um...
Well, I was going through a really hard time in London...
...what with my brother getting married and that guy thinking I was Ross' mother.
Right.
Well, anyway, I just...
That night meant a lot to me. And I guess I'm trying to say thanks.
You know, that night meant a lot to me too.
And it wasn't because I was in a bad place or anything.
It just meant a lot to me because you're really hot.
Is that okay?
Ha, ha. That's okay.
And I'm cute too?
And you're cute too.
Thank you.
All right, I got to go unpack.
Okay.
Bye.
I'm still on London time. Does that count?
Oh, that counts.
Oh, good.
Rach.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Well, I've been on standby for a flight home for hours.
Oh.
Oh. So no sign of Emily, huh?
Not yet.
So, um...
What time are you supposed to leave?
This is the last call for Flight 1066 to Athens.
The last call.
Pretty soon, I guess.
I'm sorry.
I just... I don't understand. I mean, how could she do this?
What, am I like a complete idiot...
...for thinking she'd actually show up?
No.
You're not an idiot, Ross.
You're a guy very much in love.
Same difference.
All passengers for Flight 1066 to Athens should now be onboard.
I get it!
Well, that's that.
No, you know what?
I think you should go.
What?
Yeah, I do think you should go...
...by yourself. Get some distance.
Clear your head. I think it would be really good.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, come on, Ross. I think it would be really good for you.
I could. I could do that.
Yeah.
I can't even believe her.
You know what? I am going to go.
Good.
Why not?
Right?
Right. Right.
Thanks.
Okay, I'll see you back at home.
If I ever get a flight out of here.
Hey, well...
No.
What? Wait, what?
Why don't you come?
I mean, I have two tickets. Why not?
Well, I don't know, Ross. Really?
Yeah, yeah. It'd be great. I mean, you can...
You can lay on the beach...
...and I can cry over my failed marriage.
You see how I make jokes?
Uh-huh.
Really. I mean...
God, I could use a friend.
Oh, wow. Okay, maybe.
Um...
Yes, I can do that.
All right, cool.
Okay, we're going to Greece. Yeah, okay.
Aah, aah. I forgot my jacket.
Well, you tell them to wait.
Okay.
Wait. Wait.
Emily.
Oh, no, no, no.
No! No!
Emily!
Ah, yes. I will have a glass of the Merlot...
...and he will have a white-wine spritzer.
Hey, look at that. The airport's moving.
Hey, are we moving?
Are we moving? Why are we moving?
They... Um...
Yeah, does the captain know that we're moving?
Oh, my gosh.